faistapart.ca 2015-09-26

# Privacy Notice : Cheap Clothing of La Martina,LACOSTE,Paul Shark,Ralph Lauren,Tommy Hilfiger Sale Canada Online

1.How can protegersu 

privacy? 

The security of your personal information nosotros.Nunca important esmuy sell or rent your informaciÃ³npersonal to third parties under any circunstancia.Valoramos very high confidence, and will work to protect the security and privacy of personal cualquierinformaciÃ³n you provide and only hemosdescrito will use as our Privacy Policy. 

During 

Infomessages exchange, we will do everything possible to ensure the security of encryption suinformaciÃ³n by the input information with the software deseguridad Socket Layer (SSL).'s very important to prevent other people from using your password noautorizadas or enter equipo.Por therefore debeasegurar immediate stop off after webcuando visit the same computer is shared with others. 

2\. What informaciÃ³npersonal of users that we collect? 

Our primary goal is to staff recopilarinformaciÃ³n customize and enhance nuestrosservicios.Recogemos the following types of information from our users: 

information you provide to us: 

We receive and store 

cualquierinformaciÃ³n you enter on our website or give us in otramanera, such as your name, email address and other proporciona.Usted informationthat you may choose to provide us ciertainformaciÃ³n, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many know about our special features, such as posting commentsin our websites, creating a user or receive alerts correoelectrÃ³nico.La personal information you provide will utilizadapara such purposes as responding to your requests for certain IT products and services, personalize the advertising content you see and communicate. 

3\. How to use theinformation we collect. 

â—† 

Podemosutilizar the information we collect to: 

* Operate, provide, improve and maintain the website 

* Customize and / or personalize your communications and experience decompra 

* Better respond to your customer service questions 

* Communicate with you about your purchase, account information or customer needs serviciode 

* Communicate with you about our products and events, and promotional otrosfines 

* Improve our business 

* Administer contests, promotions, surveys or other WebSite 

â—† 

Nosotrosutilizamos cookies to: 

* Remember the items in your shopping cart 

* Recognize that when you return to our website 

* Store your username or login email (but not yourpassword) to facilitate the entry 

* Confirm that users are logged in 

* Lepermiten use Checkout Express 

* Analyze visitor behavior 

Notice: 

If you do not wish to accept cookies, puedebloquearlas by adjusting your browser settings to Internet.Sinembargo, if blocks will not be able to use all the characteristics of our web sites, including the customizations features asociadascon creating a user profile. 

4\. Your Consent 

â—† At utilizarnuestro 

site, you agree to our privacy policy. 

â—† 

Alconvertirse a member of our website, you agree to share unimporte base of information with the rest of the community, including your username, laubicaciÃ³n of laciudad, profile picture and certain information bÃ¡sica.Con elfin to participate in all additional Web features and community andthe exchange activities, have to change their privacy settings to share more information, including all contenidogenerado by the user, your profile page and all your activity on the website.
